Spain, well, the one that has sponsored this
España pues la que ha patrocinado esta
shitty reality show that is going to be now,
de reality que va a haber ahora a
where Jorge Pérez is going and Cristina contributes
la que va Jorge Pérez y Cristina aporta
and by the way, it seems to me what
y que por cierto me da la impresión qué
Jorge is going to earn spoiler, I tell you this
va a ganar Jorge spoiler os lo digo
because you also have to work
porque es que también hay que trabajar
with people who don't talk too much, what
con gente que no se vaya de la boca lo
happens is that since you pay poorly, well,
que pasa es que como pagáis mal Pues
nobody is loyal to you because if there is little, but there
nadie os es fiel Porque si hay poco pero
is little for everyone, then people are such and such,
hay poco para todos pues la gente tal
but of course when they see that there is money for
pero claro cuando ve que hay dinero para
some and not for others, people get
unos y para otros no con la gente se
angry. A person who
cabrea me ha escrito una persona que
is in contact with Mediaset wrote to me to
está en contacto con mediaset para
tell me please don't say that Jorge has
decirme por favor no digas que Jorge Ha
won the reality show because there are many people
ganado el reality porque hay mucha gente
who have worked on that reality show, you are
que ha trabajado en ese reality te estás
risking their bread, that the program is
jugando su pan que el programa está
recorded, that Jorge has already won, that he has
grabado que ya ha ganado Jorge que lo ha
leaked it, that the program is recorded. I
filtrado que el programa está grabado O
mean, I haven't passed it's that it's recorded, I
sea no he pasado es que está grabado
can't believe it, what a [ __ ]
no me lo puedo creer vaya puñetera
machine, I didn't know it was recorded. I
máquina yo no sabía que estaba grabado O
mean, I thought that there was going to be commentary on, you know,
sea yo pensé que se iba a comentar sabes
like Temptation Island with some
como la isla de la tentación con algún
presenter and some debate, Iran
presentador Y algún debate Irán
commenting on it, but what is the reality show
comentándolo pero lo que es el reality
is recorded. How shameless are you
está grabado Qué poca vergüenza tenéis
that on top of that you are asking me for things
que encima me estáis pidiendo cosas
when  I didn't like it at all
cuando a mí no me ha gustado nada